[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Barong is the embroidered formal garment of which country in South-East Asia?", "correct_answer": "The Philippines", "incorrect_answers": ["Russia", "Indonesia", "Japan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the protagonist of John Boormans 1998 movie The General?", "correct_answer": "Martin Cahill, a criminal from Dublin, Ireland", "incorrect_answers": ["Pablo Escobar, a Columbian drug lord", "Idi Amin, a dictator of Uganda", "Gulbuddin Hekmatyar, a Taliban warlord"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Marilyn Mansons 1995 remix album in which he included his cover of Eurythmics 1983 Sweet Dreams (Are Made of This)?", "correct_answer": "Smells Like Children", "incorrect_answers": ["Portrait of an American Family", "Antichrist Superstar", "The Last Tour on Earth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the atomic number of Neon?", "correct_answer": "10", "incorrect_answers": ["11", "13", "12"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to Wizard magazine, where did Freddy Krueger rate on the list of all time greatest movie villains?", "correct_answer": "14th", "incorrect_answers": ["9th", "3rd", "1st"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Brandon Lee was killed during the shooting of the film The Crow while doing what scene?", "correct_answer": "a flashback scene", "incorrect_answers": ["a guns blazing scene", "a police chase scene", "a roof stunt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Popcorn is flavored with salt, butter, sugar, dried spices and many other condiments. In this country they even serve it with vinegar.", "correct_answer": "Sweden", "incorrect_answers": ["France", "Italy", "Belgium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How are the people having rectangular palms, flushed skin and short fingers classified according to palmistry?", "correct_answer": "Fire", "incorrect_answers": ["Dragon", "Storm", "Summer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of these French Kings was not a founder of a royal dynasty.  Which one?", "correct_answer": "Louis XIII the Well-Beloved", "incorrect_answers": ["Hugh Capet", "Philip VI the Fortunate", "Charles the Bald"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the origin of the word cactus?", "correct_answer": "Greek", "incorrect_answers": ["Portuguese", "German", "Mexican (Spanish)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This island, located north of Australia, is the second-largest island on the planet.", "correct_answer": "New Guinea", "incorrect_answers": ["Tasmania", "South Island", "Sri Lanka"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following components of the atom is not considered an elementary particle?", "correct_answer": "Proton", "incorrect_answers": ["Quark", "Electron", "Gluon"]}]